# KRISTINA VRAGOVIC

#### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

From publishing to marketing to web development, my career has been a journey of considering great ideas from authors, teams, and peers and helping them come to life. I'm motivated by inclusive, high-energy teams that foster curiosity and growth.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## **Dev Bootcamp**

#### Mentor

Aug. 2017 - Present I help students to learn new programming concepts and tech stacks through the socratic method and pair programming.

#### **Dev Bootcamp**

#### Student

Apr. - Aug. 2017

This intensive training program for web developers focuses on OOD, TDD, empathetic teamwork, and pair programming.

## **Association of Legal Administrators**

#### Copywriter/Editor

Feb. 2015 - May 2017

Wrote and designed HTML/CSS emails and email templates and produced microsites for association events in house CMS and style.

## **North American Company for Life and Health Insurance**

#### **Marketing Communications Specialist**

Apr. 2013 - Feb. 2015

Brainstormed, planned, and managed digital marketing campaigns; edited emails and landing pages in HTML/CSS.

260-241-8098

k.vragovic@gmail.com Chicago, IL 60626

in kvragovic ( kvrag



# SKILLS

Ruby on Rails with ActiveRecord JavaScript, ¡Query, and AJAX HTML5 and CSS3 Object-oriented design Test-driven development Agile collaboration and Git workflow Database management (Postgres, SQL)

## **PROJECTS**

### **Grown (Rails app for garden planning)**

In development: *github.com/kvrag/grown* 

#### **Unstuck (cross-platform mobile app)**

#### **Team Lead**

July - Aug. 2017

- Ionic/Cordova, Angular JS, Rails, HTML, CSS
- Natural Language Processing with Emoj API Pitched idea and led four-person team to build self-care/mental health app in one week. github.com/kvrag/whats-next-app

#### **Game Knight (BoardGameGeek clone)**

#### **Project Manager**

July 2017

- Rails, Paperclip, CSS, JavaScript Led vertical, Agile-style workflow on team of four DBC peers with three-day turnaround. game-knight-dbc-3.herokuapp.com

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Indiana University Bloomington**

B.A. English (Economics, Management)